<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<game>
	<title>RunGunJumpGun</title>
<release-date>Summer 2016</release-date>
	<website>http://rungunjumpgun.com</website>
	<press-can-request-copy>TRUE</press-can-request-copy>
	<prices>
	  <price>
	    <currency>USD</currency>
	    <value>TBA</value>
	    </price>
	  <price>
	    <currency>EUR</currency>
	    <value>TBA</value>
	    </price>
	  <price>
	    <currency>CAD</currency>
	    <value>TBA</value>
	  </price>
	  <price>
	    <currency>GBP</currency>
	    <value>TBA</value>
	    </price>
	  </prices>


	<platforms>
		<platform>
			<name>Steam</name>
			<link>http://store.steampowered.com/app/440550</link>
		</platform>
	</platforms>
	
	<description>
RUNGUNJUMPGUN is a retro-style 2D automatic-runner with two-button controls. One button let’s you fly, the other blasts your obstacles into heaps of rubble. There is no stopping in RUNGUNJUMPGUN’s surreal fantasy-sci-fi world. There is only running, gunning, jumping, and gunning.	
</description>
	
	<history>
The team behind RUNGUNJUMPGUN met as co-workers at a marketing company in Alberta, Canada. When Matthew and Logan (artist and programmer) left the company in late 2014, they planned to create a small video game as a farewell card to their colleagues; something cute with everyone’s face in it and lots of heartwarming inside jokes. Jordan joined shortly after to compose music and act as writer for the project as the scope of RunGunJumpGun expanded into a full title (a full title in desperate need of sweltering hot jams and a story for the ages). The trio worked out of their local library's makerspace for the summer, before moving into a co-working space based out of an old whiskey storage warehouse near the end of the year. RunGunJumpGun was Greenlit for distribution on the Steam Marketplace in December 2015. 
	</history>
		<features>
<feature>Merciful respawns let you die with efficiency and keep you in the game.</feature>
<feature>Three brutal worlds full of meticulously crafted levels created by the shrewdest level-artisans, designed to hone and test the player’s speed and tenacity.</feature>
<feature>Accessible single-hand gameplay appropriate for players with disabilities.</feature>
<feature>Tripped-out hyper-colourful fantasy-sci-fi art style</feature>
<feature>Pulsing musical score blending hip hop, electronic and movie-score vibes.</feature>
<feature>Warped space-opera narrative and a cast of crazed, beautifully illustrated characters.</feature>
<feature>The quest to collect “Atomiks” littered throughout levels lends an extra level of insanity to already merciless level design. A gift to self-hating completionists.</feature>
<feature>Made by free range developers fed a pure mixture of VVVVVV, Hotline Miami, and Super Meat Boy.</feature>
</features>	
	
	
	<quotes>
		<quote>
			<description>Pulsing stages filled with brilliant color, screen-shaking gunfire, and pounding sound.</description>
			<name>Joel Couture</name>
			<website>IndieGames.com</website>
			<link>http://indiegames.com/2015/12/bathe_in_the_intensity_of_rung.html</link>
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<description>Looks to be absolutely brutal. And colorful too. You can't ignore those vibrant colors.</description>
			<name>Chris Priestman</name>
			<website>Siliconera.com</website>
			<link>http://www.siliconera.com/2015/12/11/rungunjumpgun-aims-to-push-your-run-n-gun-skills-to-the-limit/</link>
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<description>'Solar Jetman' on speed 
and LSD</description>
			<name>Robin Ek</name>
			<website>TheGG.Net</website>
			<link>http://thegg.net/indie-games/thirtythree-games-super-intense-action-game-rungunjumpgun-is-set-for-an-early-2016-release/</link>
		</quote>
		
	</quotes>

	<trailers>
		<trailer>
			<name>Steam Greenlight Trailer</name>
			<youtube>53PjRtfr_xY</youtube>
		</trailer>
		<trailer>
			<name>Early Gameplay Video</name>
			<youtube>4agvAM0CGf8</youtube>
		</trailer>
	</trailers>

																	 	monetize (full permission) -->	
	<additionals>
		<additional>
			<title>Steam Greenlight</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=559207299</link>
		</additional>
		<additional>
			<title>Soundtrack</title>
			<link>https://soundcloud.com/rockliffandcompany/sets/rungunjumpgun-soundtrack-sampler</link>
		</additional>
	</additionals>
	

	<credits>
		<credit>
		  <person>Logan Gilmour</person>
			<role>Programmer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Matthew Satchwill</person>
			<role>Art and animation</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Jordan Bloemen</person>
			<role>Music and story</role>
		</credit>
	</credits>
	
	
</game>
